Guide to the Men's Basketball Game Film Collection, 1947-1996 UA.13.01.0005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Men's Basketball Game Film Collection
1947-1996
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University Dept. of Athletics
UA.13.01.0005
303 Linear Feet
The Men's Basketball Game Film Collection includes films of Duke basketball games from the 1940s through the 1990s created by Duke Athletics for use by coaches.
Access Restrictions
Portions of this collection are unprocessed and may require screening, arrangement, and/or rehousing before use.
Conditions Governing Access
Use of audiotapes and videotapes from this collection requires the creation of reference copies. Reference copies for some materials may have been made, and if a reference copy exists, it is noted in this finding aid. To arrange for the creation of reference copies of other items, please contact University Archives staff. Although these recordings are now stored in a stable environment, their condition and playback quality is unknown.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged chronologically by date of game.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Several accessions were combined into this collection guide. Materials were transferred from Duke Athletics over a period of years.
Scope and Contents
The Men's Basketball Game Film collection contains recordings of Duke Blue Devils men's basketball games created by Duke Athletics for the use of coaches and departmental staff. Recordings made before 1990 are largely on 16mm cellulose acetate film, and may be black and white or color and with or without audio; indications of color film or with included audio are noted in this guide where known. Recordings are grouped by individual game, titled by opponent, and include information on the game's outcome, score, and location, where known. Reference copies in other formats are included for a given game where they exist. Recordings made after 1989 are largely on video formats including VHS, BetaCam, and DVCam.
Also included are some compilations of games, highlights for certain players, and some recordings made from broadcast television. Not every game played by Duke Men's Basketball is included in this collection. Most games were recorded on several film reels, and some are missing. Many films have likely been edited.
Additional information on location or game events may be included on the containers of individual recordings, or in the recordings themselves.
Basketball; Duke University. Department of Athletics; Duke Blue Devils (Basketball team)
- Men's Basketball Game Films
  - NYU, 1947 January 01
    - Duke vs. NYU: Reel 1, 1947 January 01; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 197, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0001)
  - NYU, 1948 January 08
    - Duke vs. NYU: Reel 1, 1948 January 08; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 165, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0002)
  - Basketball Highlights, 1948 April 01
    Scope and Contents
    Approximate date. This is newsreel footage of pro teams.
    - Basketball Highlights: Reel 1, 1948 April 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 162, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0003)
  - Maryland, 1949 January 03
    Duke win; score: 58-46
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1949 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 162, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0004)
  - NC State, 1950 January 07
    Duke win; score: 58-55
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1950 January 07; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 164, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0005)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 January 07; U-matic
      Duplication Master
  - NYU, 1950 January 12
    Duke loss; score: 64-80
    - Duke vs. NYU: Reel 1, 1950 January 12; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 164, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0006)
  - Navy, 1950 February 04
    Duke win; score: 68-53
    - Duke vs. Navy: Reel 1, 1950 February 04; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 201, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0007)
  - NC State, 1950 March 04
    Duke loss; score: 47-67
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1950 March 04; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 201, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0008)
  - Wake Forest, 1952 December 06
    Duke loss; score: 86-91
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1952 December 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 163, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0009)
  - NC State, 1953 January 10
    Duke loss; score: 64-82
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1953 January 10; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 165, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0010)
  - South Carolina, 1953 February 21
    Duke win; score: 98-68
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 1, 1953 February 21; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 202, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0011)
  - North Carolina, 1953 February 27
    Duke win; score: 83-58
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1953 February 27; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 165, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0012)
  - William & Mary, 1953 December 12
    Duke win; score: 109-44
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 1, 1953 December 12; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 197, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0014)
  - Maryland, circa 1954-1955
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, circa 1954-1955; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 162, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0018)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, circa 1954-1955; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 162, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0016)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, circa 1954-1955; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 162, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0017)
  - NC State, circa 1954-1955
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, circa 1954-1955; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 162, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0015)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1 (2?), circa 1954-1955; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 163, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0023)
  - South Carolina, circa 1954-1955
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 1, circa 1954-1955; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 162, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0019)
  - Virginia, circa 1954-1955
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, circa 1954-1955; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 196, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0024)
  - NC State, 1954 January 09
    Duke win; score: 87-85
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1954 January 09; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 197, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0025)
  - George Washington, 1954 February 06
    Duke loss; score: 71-76
    - Duke vs. George Washington: Reel 1, 1954 February 06; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 195, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0026)
  - West Virginia, 1955 December 27
    1954 Dixie Classic. VHS mislabelled as "55-56"
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 1, 1955 December 27; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 196, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0027)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 1, 1955 December 27; VHS
  - George Washington, circa 1955-1956
    - Duke vs. George Washington: Reel 1, circa 1955-1956; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 162, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0028)
  - NC State, 1955 October 01
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1955 October 01; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 197, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0029)
  - North Carolina, 1955 December 30
    Duke loss; score 74-64; at Raleigh Memorial
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel, 1955 December 30; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 195, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3477)
  - Kent State, 1956 January 01
    - Duke vs. Kent State: Reel 1, circa 1956-1957; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 196, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0036)
  - NC State, circa 1956-1957
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, circa 1956-1957; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 164, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0030)
      Game played at NCSU
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, circa 1956-1957; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0031)
      Played at Duke
  - North Carolina, circa 1956-1957
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, circa 1956-1957; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0032)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, circa 1956-1957; 16mm film: 5" reel (Box 172, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0035)
  - West Virginia, 1956 December 27
    Duke win; score: 73-67; Dixie Classic
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 3, 1956 December 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 198, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0037)
  - Maryland, circa 1957-1958
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, circa 1957-1958; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0038)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, circa 1957-1958; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0039)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, circa 1957-1958; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 196, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0040)
  - Villanova, circa 1957-1958
    - Duke vs. Villanova: Reel 1, circa 1957-1958; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 196, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0041)
  - Maryland, 1957 January 31
    Duke win; score: 72-60
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1957 January 31; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 164, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0042)
  - Temple, 1957 December 01
    - Duke vs. Temple: Reel 1, 1957 December 01; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 165, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0043)
  - Wake Forest, 1957 December 28
    Duke win; score: 79-75; Dixie Classic
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1957 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0045)
  - NC State, circa 1958-1959
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, circa 1958-1959; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0046)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, circa 1958-1959; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0047)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, circa 1958-1959; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0048)
  - North Carolina, circa 1958-1959
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, circa 1958-1959; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0049)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, circa 1958-1959; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0050)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, circa 1958-1959; 16mm film: 5" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0051)
  - South Carolina, circa 1958-1959
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 1, circa 1958-1959; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0052)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 2, circa 1958-1959; 16mm film: 5" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0053)
  - Michigan State, 1959 December 29
    Duke loss; score: 57-82
    - Duke vs. Michigan State: Reel 1, 1959 December 29; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 195, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0054)
  - North Carolina, 1960 March 04
    Duke win; score: 71-69
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1960 March 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0055)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1960 March 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0056)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1960 March 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0057)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1960 March 04; DVD
  - Princeton, 1960 March 08
    Duke win; score: 84-60
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 1, 1960 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0058)
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 2, 1960 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0059)
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 3, 1960 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0060)
  - Louisiana State, 1960 December 03
    Duke win; score: 80-74
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 1, 1960 December 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0061)
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 2, 1960 December 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0062)
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 3, 1960 December 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0063)
  - South Carolina, 1960 December 12
    Duke win; score: 107-79
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 1, 1960 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0064)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 2, 1960 December 12; 16mm film: 5" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0065)
  - Clemson, 1960 December 15
    Duke win; score: 75-58
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1960 December 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0066)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1960 December 15; 16mm film: 5" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0067)
  - Wyoming, 1960 December 29
    Duke win; score: 86-59
    - Duke vs. Wyoming: Reel 1, 1960 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0068)
  - Marquette, 1960 December 30
    Duke win; score: 86-73
    - Duke vs. Marquette: Reel 1, 1960 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0069)
  - North Carolina, 1960 December 31
    Duke loss; score: 71-76; 4 Reels, 1 is un-numbered, rest are numbered 1-3 (original numbering scheme)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1960 December 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0070)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1960 December 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0071)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1960 December 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0072)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1960 December 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0073)
  - Citadel
    - Duke vs. Citadel: Reel 1, circa 1961; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 172, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0074)
    - Duke vs. Citadel: Reel 2, circa 1961; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 172, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0075)
    - Duke vs. Citadel: Reel 3, circa 1961; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 172, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0076)
    - Duke vs. Citadel: Reel 4, circa 1961; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 172, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0077)
  - NC State, 1961 January 07
    Duke win; score: 81-67
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1961 January 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0078)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1961 January 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0079)
  - Maryland, 1961 January 14
    Duke win; score: 70-62
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1961 January 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0080)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1961 January 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0081)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1961 January 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 167, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0082)
  - North Carolina, 1961 February 04
    Duke win; score: 81-77
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1961 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0083)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1961 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0084)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1961 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0085)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1961 February 04; DVD
  - NYU, 1961 February 04
    - Duke vs. NYU: Reel 1, 1961 February 04; 16mm film: 3" reel (Box 198, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0086)
  - NC State, 1961 February 07
    Duke loss; score: 59-61
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1961 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0088)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1961 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0089)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1961 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0090)
  - Virginia, 1961 February 20
    Duke win; score: 77-66
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1961 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0091)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1961 February 20; 16mm film: 5" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0092)
  - Wake Forest, 1961 March 04
    Duke loss; score: 81-96; Incomplete. Reel labelled #3 was shot from a TV screen; there is no sound track.
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1961 March 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0148)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1961 March 04; DVD
      Reference copy
  - Florida, 1961 December 01
    Duke win; score: 80-58
    - Duke vs. Florida: Reel 1, 1961 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0095)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Reel 2, 1961 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0096)
  - Davidson, 1961 December 05
    Duke win; score: 117-72
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 1, 1961 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0097)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 2, 1961 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0098)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 3, 1961 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0099)
  - Clemson, 1961 December 11
    Duke win; score: 89-66
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1961 December 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0100)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1961 December 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0101)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1961 December 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0102)
  - West Virginia, 1961 December 18
    Duke win; score: 69-65
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 1, 1961 December 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0103)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 2, 1961 December 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0104)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 3, 1961 December 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 168, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0105)
  - Quantico, circa 1962
    Scrimmage
    - Duke vs. Quantico: Reel 1, 1962 January 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 172, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0106)
    - Duke vs. Quantico: Reel 2, 1962 January 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 172, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0107)
    - Duke vs. Quantico: Reel 3, 1962 January 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 172, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0108)
  - Penn State, 1962 January 03
    Duke win; score: 95-55
    - Duke vs. Penn State: Reel 1, 1962 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0109)
    - Duke vs. Penn State: Reel 2, 1962 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0110)
    - Duke vs. Penn State: Reel 3, 1962 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0111)
  - NC State, 1962 January 06
    Duke loss; score: 60-61
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1962 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0112)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1962 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0113)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1962 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0114)
  - Maryland, 1962 January 13
    Duke win; score: 84-68
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1962 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0115)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1962 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0116)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1962 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0117)
  - Wake Forest, 1962 January 27
    Duke win; score: 82-68
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1962 January 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0118)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1962 January 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0119)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1962 January 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0120)
  - South Carolina, 1962 January 30
    Duke win; score: 89-73
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 1, 1962 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0121)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 2, 1962 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0122)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 3, 1962 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0123)
  - North Carolina, 1962 February 03
    Duke win; score: 79-57
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1962 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0124)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1962 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0125)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1962 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0126)
  - Virginia, 1962 February 10
    Duke win; score: 101-75
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1962 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0127)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1962 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0128)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1962 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0129)
  - Navy, 1962 February 17
    Duke win; score: 91-72
    - Duke vs. Navy: Reel 1, 1962 February 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0130)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Reel 2, 1962 February 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0131)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Reel 3, 1962 February 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 170, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0132)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unknown game film coverage, 1962 February 17; DVD
      Duplication master
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unknown game film coverage, 1962 February 17; DVD
  - Clemson, 1962 March 02
    Duke loss; score: 72-77
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1962 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 172, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0133)
  - Davidson, 1962 December 01
    Duke win; score: 76-68
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 1, 1962 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0134)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 2, 1962 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0135)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 3, 1962 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0136)
  - South Carolina, 1962 December 04
    Duke win; score: 95-63
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 1, 1962 December 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0137)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 2, 1962 December 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0138)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 3, 1962 December 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0139)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 4, 1962 December 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 169, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0140)
  - Maryland, 1962 December 08
    Duke win; score: 92-56
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1962 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 192, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0141)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1962 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 192, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0142)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1962 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 192, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0143)
  - Vanderbilt, 1962 December 11
    Duke win; score: 90-70
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Reel 1, 1962 December 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0144)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Reel 2, 1962 December 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0145)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Reel 3, 1962 December 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0146)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Reel 4, 1962 December 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0147)
  - Clemson, 1962 December 13
    Duke win; score: 92-67
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1962 December 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0094)
  - Princeton, 1962 December 28
    Duke win; score: 85-74
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 1, 1962 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0149)
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 2, 1962 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0150)
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 3, 1962 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0151)
  - Wake Forest, 1962 December 29
    Duke win; score: 113-87
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1962 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0152)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1962 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0153)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1962 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 171, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0154)
  - All America Team, 1963
    Outcome unknown; black and white.
    - All America Team: Unknown game film coverage, 1963; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 198, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0155)